<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Services on Pseudonymisieren</title>
    <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Services on Pseudonymisieren</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Developed by DataFortress.cloud UG</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scan your data for GDPR compliance with our web interface and API</title>
      <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/sensitive-data-scanning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/sensitive-data-scanning/</guid>
      <description>Effortlessly Achieve GDPR Compliance with Our Web Interface and API Scanning Solution Scanning your data for GDPR compliance can be a daunting task, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with the regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On-premise GDPR compliance with our data landscape scanning solution</title>
      <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/on-premise-sensitive-data-scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/on-premise-sensitive-data-scanner/</guid>
      <description>Achieving On-premise GDPR Compliance: Let Our Data Landscape Scanning Tool Help As businesses navigate the ever-evolving landscape of data privacy regulations, it&amp;rsquo;s increasingly important to ensure that your organization is fully compliant with GDPR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDPR-compliant managed SQL instances hosted in Germany with built-in anonymization</title>
      <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/gdpr-sql-instances/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/gdpr-sql-instances/</guid>
      <description>Secure Your Data with GDPR-compliant Managed SQL Instances Hosted in Germany When it comes to data privacy and compliance, one of the most important considerations is the physical location of your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data compliance consultation</title>
      <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/data-compliance-consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/data-compliance-consultation/</guid>
      <description>Ensure GDPR Compliance with Our Expert Consultation Services Ensuring compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) can be a daunting task for any organization, especially when it comes to sensitive data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETL data pipelines. Let us transform and combine your data.</title>
      <link>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/data-pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pseudonymisieren.de/services/data-pipelines/</guid>
      <description>Streamline Your Data Management: Let Us Optimize Your ETL Pipelines Data management is a critical aspect of any business, and it&amp;rsquo;s only getting more complex as the volume of data grows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
